makeup-mania.net 2017-11-21

# Privacy Policy | Makeup Mania

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Makeup Mania collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the <http://makeup-mania.net/>  website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Gossip World.

Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, subscribe to the newsletter, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

Web browser cookies

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

  * Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to your website.
  * Google’s use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users that are based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites across the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of using the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/settings/ads?hl=en&sig=ACi0TCjbhRob14Ol82kIMbbHjOYdgb1cBdhrmTtz1mQTW2djj7R6r0-PenzFo6JSvqV8_51Hr9Z_Ze_WqPnQ2MIl2Hcvt1DiMX65eJ5AI9bB096WH1B2Wci-_7WpDylSUpoM2rnojtRbl_il0BlMiCkL3H5IzuO7e9cxyj6vuR5eXTzb01kHKIJSfEhWzpj3yERXNoAgMkXA). (Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies for interest-based advertising by visiting [aboutads.info.)](http://www.aboutads.info/)

If you have not [opted out of third-party ad serving](https://support.google.com/dfp_sb/answer/94152?hl=en-GB), the cookies of other [third-party vendors or ad networks ](https://support.google.com/dfp_sb/answer/94149?hl=en-GB)may also be used to serve ads on your site, and should be disclosed in your privacy policy in the following manner.

  * Notify your site visitors of the third-party vendors and ad networks serving ads on your site.
  * Provide links to the appropriate vendor and ad network websites.
  * Inform your users that they may visit those websites to opt out of the use of cookies for interest-based advertising (if the vendor or ad network offers this capability). Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of some third-party vendors’ use of cookies for interest-based advertising by visiting [aboutads.info.](http://www.aboutads.info/)

Because publisher sites and laws across countries vary, we’re unable to suggest specific privacy policy language. However, you may wish to review resources such as the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) for guidance on drafting a privacy policy.

How we use collected information

Makeup Mania collects and uses Users personal information for the following purposes:  
– To personalize user experience  
We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.  
– To improve our Site  
We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.  
– To improve customer service  
Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.  
– To share your information with third parties  
We may share or sell information with third parties for marketing or other purposes.  
– To administer a content, promotion, survey or other Site feature  
To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.  
– To send periodic emails  
The email address Users provide for order processing, will only be used to send them information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, they may do so by contacting us via our Site.  
How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

Third party websites

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

Google Adsense

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at [http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

Changes to this privacy policy

Makeup Mania  has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site, revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:
